<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Maker Park</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 22:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 22:30:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.3.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>GreenPointers on Maker Park</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;From GreenPointers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;While the city is still 11 acres away from fulfilling its promise to deliver all 28 acres of Bushwick Inlet Park, it took a 7 acre step in the right direction this year by purchasing the remaining parcel of the Bayside Fuel Property. With it came ten 50ft tall cylindrical iron fuel containers and a three story brick building, which the city intends to demolish in favor of flat open space. But will that be an end of an opportunity to repurpose these structures and integrate them into the landscaping of the park? The founders of Maker Park think so and want to start a conversation with the wider-community about adaptively reusing these structures in a way that serves the creative ethos of North Brooklyn.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://greenpointers.com/2016/07/12/maker-park-envisions-a-public-creative-space-in-bushwick-inlet-park/&quot;&gt;Continue reading the story&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 18:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/news/2016/07/12/greenpointers-on-maker-park/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/news/2016/07/12/greenpointers-on-maker-park/</guid>
        
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Curbed New York on Maker Park</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;From Curbed:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As plans for a 28-acre park along the Williamsburg waterfront continue to languish, an alternative idea has emerged to transform the former industrial area along Bushwick Inlet. DNAinfo spoke with the developers behind Maker Park — a plan to redevelop a plot along the inlet into a space for artists and greenhouses.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ny.curbed.com/2016/5/31/11818738/williamsburg-bushwick-inlet-park-maker-park&quot;&gt;Continue reading the story&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 18:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/news/2016/05/31/curbed-on-maker-park/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/news/2016/05/31/curbed-on-maker-park/</guid>
        
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The New York Times on Maker Park</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;From the Times:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;New York City abhors a vacuum. And, in some ways, the scraggly parkland along the Bushwick Inlet in Brooklyn, pocked with industrial ruins and warehouses where a 28-acre park was to be born, is exactly that. It is a hole in the cityscape, waiting to be filled.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;So it makes sense that as the city continues to struggle to make good on a more than decade-old promise to develop the park — stymied by its inability to acquire all the necessary land and slowed by the laborious process of cleaning up the area’s legacy of industrial grime — a competing idea has arisen, sprouting through the cracks in the process like weeds through a sidewalk…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/2016/05/31/nyregion/disparate-visions-for-a-brooklyn-park-dismantle-industrial-ruins-or-preserve-them.html?_r=0&quot;&gt;Continue reading the story&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- ![oilworks](/images/historic/charles-pratt.jpg){:class=&quot;post__image&quot;} --&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 18:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/news/2016/05/30/new-york-times-on-maker-park/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/news/2016/05/30/new-york-times-on-maker-park/</guid>
        
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
